Seino
Galigari Channel GOGO!
Today's project is
I tried to do it with ideal white
This is
This is...
We did that Valentine's Day project a little while ago, but aren't our voices the smallest today?
It's a little bit disgusting, but... we were forced to do it... on Valentine's Day, the four of us said we'd do it next time on our own.
The next White Day, the other four will do it.
So it's not intentional. It's environmental.
It's the environment.
But what is the ideal White Day?
It's difficult, isn't it? Difficult acting.
That's right.
Have you ever received one?
White Day?
I don't remember.
Uh...
Maybe it was just for work or something.
I don't know.
I think I felt it then.
That feeling.
I remember, but...
I really don't.
It's idealistic, and it's about what you want to get out of it.
Yes, that's okay.
Okay.
Well, let's just use this green light.
I'll do my best.
Yes, sir.
Where are we going today?
Anywhere is fine.
Anywhere?
Let's go to a park around the corner.
A park?
A park is fine.
You always do.
Let's go back to the beginning.
We've been together since elementary school.
That's right.
It's been ten years.
I miss these swings.
Are we there yet?
We used to ride on the swings together.
Let's go on the swings.
We used to ride together on the swings.
You remember that?
Yeah, I remember.
That's when we said...
We said we'd be together in the future.
We said that.
I remember.
You knocked your front tooth.
I had to come down and do it.
It's been a long time since I've had my teeth filled.
We went to the dentist together.
I know you remember.
So, are you ready for dinner?
Already?
Dinner?
I have dinner reservations... for today.
Really?
Really? - Yeah.
That's great.
Let's go.
I'll just take the bullet train.
Bullet train?
No, no, no.
It's starting.
Wait, wait.
Here we are.
Okinawa.
Okinawa?
It's on the bullet train.
But... you have to go to Fukuoka.
And change trains.
Here I am in Okinawa.
They don't give a shit.
It's hot.
At night
At night.
Dinner Okinawa.
Yes, but do you want to see the ocean at night?
I'm fine.
Shall we?
Well, take a look.
Nice clouds.
Okay, well, write your name down or something.
We're all on the same site.
All right.
Love.
Yay!
Okinawa Misaki
Well, it's almost time to go, let's go to dinner.
I'm looking forward to it!
Okay, close your eyes and walk.
Close your eyes and walk.
Okay, okay.
I'm scared of Okinawa.
Close your eyes.
Fine dining.
Here we are.
It's White Day!
Yay!
Cake!
Cake.
Cake from a restaurant.
Oh, cake.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Well, thank you for giving me this valentine.
It's nice of you to give me something like this in return.
Not at all. Well, eat whatever you like.
Thank you very much.
It was delicious.
No, I'll pay with credit. You can go to the bathroom.
I'm just going to say it.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Go on.
I'm sorry. Here you go.
Thank you.
Mr. Yuan.
Mr. Omoto.
Oh, good.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Yeah, it was really good, and I'm so happy about the cake.
Oh, good, good, good.
Thank you so much.
And from here.
From here.
I'm going to the hotel.
Oh?
Oh, really?
I'm so glad you made reservations.
I did.
That's great.
But you don't have a change of clothes or anything for Asia.
No.
Then let's go buy some.
Okay.
I'll go to GU and get you a version.
GU
Yes, it looks good.
Yeah, it looks good, I got a version.
OK.
Okay, I'm going to go ahead and finish it in about 10 seconds.
Yeah, that's good.
I'll see you in about 10 seconds.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, I'll wait.
One, I'm decorating.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Eight.
I think it's time for me to go in.
Oh, geez.
Congratulations, Parr.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no!
I decorated this myself.
I just did it in 10 seconds
I'm so happy. Thank you so much.
And wait, what's this?
I just realized.
How many presents do you have?
How many of these are there?
How many of these do you have?
How many of these do I have?
How many presents do I have?
How many of these gifts can I have?
How many of these
How many of these do I have?
Oh, no!
It's not good, is it?
I prepared the number of ages
Twenty.
That's right, that's right.
Thank you.
Twenty.
And for Chanel...
Chanel got the Chitty-Poppe.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Givenchy and Acne Studios.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why all this?
you'll be fine with the money
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I have credit.
I got it.
Thank you.
I thought you'd be happy.
This is the best White Day ever.
That's great.
Yeah, I'm glad.
That's it.
What's this?
What the hell is this?
I'm in trouble!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
I thought we were celebrating the day...
I'll pay the credit card and go to the bathroom or something.
3 Next Pyokumaru rar
I'll pay for the credit, and I'll go to the restroom first.
I think it's not a sepa sizi, it's just that it's hard to get into the next one.
I'm going to do more of the same, but I'm going to do three versions of this story.
I'm still working on it. Not at all.
Natural version.
Real version.
Real version. Let's do it.
Yes, okay.
Okay. Who wants to start?
Okay, okay.
Shall we?
Okay, her.
Oh, it's decided.
How do you want to do it?
Oh no, it's White Day.
You're gonna give me something, right?
No, no, no.
I'm usually nice to you.
You're lying. I know you're expecting it.
Well, I'll get you a present.
Me. Me. Me.
I'm happy. Because I love you.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Don't get your hopes up.
You want to come in?
Let's go in. Let's go in.
There's a lot of stuff here.
What are you looking at?
Jewelry.
This is so cute.
I only saw this once.
What's this?
This one is really cute, too.
Hey, hey.
You want one of those?
What do you think?
It's too expensive.
Then, can I have the necklace?
I can't. I can't.
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm leaving, really.
Wait a minute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It was fun today, wasn't it?
Thanks.
What?
What's wrong?
No, I'm not.
Something, Ron mime.
Well, I told you.
I'm the gift that keeps on giving.
Me.
Yeah, it's me.
Well, you've always been there for me.
I'm just grateful.
I'm grateful.
I'm glad.
See you.
Bye bye.
So, I let him in.
Oh, I'm a little...
I'm feeling a little...
What?
The letter?
That jewelry?
What?
Hello, Misaki?
Hello?
I found a letter and some jewelry in your hair.
Happy White Day!
Wow!
Thank you!
It's time to go.
I'm sure he'll ask about this.
No, I don't have it.
When did he put the suspense in it?
When did he put it in? - I don't know. He's a magician.
He's a magician. He's a magician by profession. He's a very blunt magician.
That's funny. That was really good.
It's good. - It's good. It's good.
I don't know. Wait, wait, wait.
Really...
I'm just going with the flow. No. What kind of girl do you have in mind?
Cold? No, more like cute. Cute and brash.
Then let's go. A showbiz girl. Showbiz girl. So we can't hold hands.
Yes, you do. You want to come to France? I don't want to come to France. I won't hold your hand.
I don't want to come to France. I won't hold your hand.
Thank you.
It's White Day, you know?
I've got a present for you.
What?
Yeah.
Really?
It's just this...
Yeah? - Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Do you know what this is?
A handkerchief?
No, it's not a handkerchief.
No, it's hard to tell.
Actually, it's perfume.
What?
I knew it! You're in show business, right?
Yes.
So I thought a necklace or an accessory would make it look like I'm trying to make it smell.
That's true.
If it's perfume, you can wear it all the time.
Yes.
I wonder if you'll think of me all the time.
Will you use it?
I will.
Oh! What? I thought we were wearing the same perfume.
No, it's not.
It's different, but...
I chose it because I thought it would suit you.
I'm so glad.
If you use it...
Can I put some on?
No, I can't.
No?
Well, maybe tomorrow...
Tomorrow.
I want you to use "tomorrow".
Okay, so I'll see you tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Don't you have work tomorrow?
No.
No work tomorrow?
I'll see you then.
Okay, I'll put it on and I'll be home.
Okay.
Ah!
Bye-bye.
Bye bye.
We're definitely not dating.
Before?
No, I'm in show business.
That's right.
Are you handing that to her out there?
Yes, I do.
Yeah, you're pretty open about it.
That's funny.
Do they smell the same to you?
No, it's simple.
I think men's and women's clothes are different.
I see.
That's true.
But aren't you so smart?
Yes.
That song...
It's so real.
It's so obvious.
But the smell, it's not so obvious, is it?
No, it's true.
Not if they don't match.
Especially when people are looking at you through a screen.
That's true.
My head.
That's how I did it.
It's so realistic.
I'm very happy to have been able to do it this way.
It's amazing.
It's so real.
Real.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes.
Bye-bye.
Let's watch TV.
What do you want to watch today?
I think we're gonna watch a live show today.
That's good. That's good.
You like that kind of stuff.
I do.
It's funny.
Isn't it funny?
It's the funniest thing I've ever heard in a chat room.
I love that kind of stuff.
You know, the teasing.
You have to work on that kind of comedy.
It's a good lesson.
I can see that.
You're always watching.
Look.
What, what, what?
Did you get it in white?
That's what I did.
Yes, I did.
That's why you gave me homemade Valentine's Day chocolates.
I gave it to you.
So bring me a letter and a present.
What?
I'll read them.
You'll read it?
Give it to me.
Yeah. - Okay.
Thank you for everything.
Those homemade chocolates you made me were so good.
I'll always love you.
Hi.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Is this a letter?
Yeah.
I'm not really good with homemade stuff.
I bought it at a store.
Will you accept my chocolate?
Chocolate? Thank you.
Okay.
Let's watch TV then.
What? Do you want some?
Here you go.
That's all.
No, no, no, no.
You're the type to give chocolate? You're the type to give chocolate?
He's already hijacked the airwaves.
Ha-ha-ha.
You talk like him.
That's great!
The most expensive movies and TV stations.
Well, I thought Okinawa was pretty expensive, too.
By bullet train.
I'm a very zealous woman.
Ideal. And she's going to Okinawa.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. And we laugh.
You'll find a lot of them.
Everyone is an ideal.
That's true. But idealistic.
Like the forest.
That's because it's on YouTube.
Because it's on YouTube.
So, like, forest, forest.
But really, it's enough just to tell her how you feel.
A letter will do.
Letters are fine, right? Letters, please.
Yes. So, that's a little...
I don't know if you enjoyed it.
I don't know if you enjoyed it, but...
Our White Day went like this.
Yes.
Did the four of you agree?
No, I'm sure we didn't.
Yes. Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
If you liked this video, please click the
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel and leave a comment.
This time I'm wearing a costume by D-Holic!